(Mrs Davis:)you'll be able to choose
(Mrs Davis:)whatever field of research
you'd like.
(Sheldon:)But if I'm a professor,
then I'll have to teach a class.
(Mrs Davis:)That is correct.
(Sheldon:)So your solution is to
promote me and pay me more money
(Sheldon:)so that I can impart
my knowledge
(Sheldon:)to the next generation
of scientists?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)You people are sick.
(knocks)
PENNY: Hey.
(Penny:)Ready to go to lunch?
(Amy:)Just give me a minute.
(Amy:)I'm stimulating the pleasure
cells of this starfish.
(Amy:)I just need to turn it off.
(Penny:)What happens
if you don't?
(Amy:)Then I have to sit through lunch
(Amy:)knowing this starfish is
having a better day than I am.
(Amy:)Is Bernadette meeting us
at the restaurant?
(Penny:)Uh, no. Actually,
I didn't invite her.
(Amy:)How come?
(Penny:)Well, ever since she helped me
get this job,
(Penny:)she won't stop bugging me.
(Amy:)Well, I think she just wants you
to do well,
(Amy:)and she's worried that you won't
(Amy:)'cause you were just
a stunningly poor waitress.